buxfor.me 2013-12-09

# BuxFor.me - Make money online by viewing advertisements

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Popcy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outpnes our privacy popcy.

Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.

We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilpng those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.

We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.

We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.

Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.

We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.

We will make readily available to customers information about our popcies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

Please acknowledge if you join this site as referral via individual referral pnk (http://www.buxfor.me/user/user/register/?id=) your email address will be visible to the person referred you to our site.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiapty of personal information is protected and maintained.
